SHIRLEY JOHNSON

DevOps engineer experienced with a variety of web and software development technologies. Seven plus yeartrack record of co I la borating with other software developers to improve processes, automate systems, and prevent downtime. Strong analytical and problem-solving skills.

19015 Gemini St, Marquette, MI 49855 s_johnson@mail.com (450)455-6790

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DEVOPS MANAGER

906Technologies, Marquette, MI March 2019 - Present

- Lead Agile team of four developers and two system administrators
- Support the development of new application features and improvements
- Create and develop Standard Operating Procedures based on common failure scenarios
- · Maintain automated CI/CD pipelines for code deployment

DEVOPS ENGINEER

Walmart Tech Services, Marquette, MI January 2017 - March 2019

- Managed 50+ Linux servers with 99.95% uptime
- Set up Docker container cluster using Kubernetes/Docker Swarm
- · Developed system for automating security updates
- · Maintained Git workflows for version control and source code management

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

University of Michigan Ann Arbor, MI September 2012 - June2016

KEY SKILLS

- Agile development
- · Continuous improvement
- Python
- JavaScript
- Git
- ♦ Kubernetes
- Docker Swarm

CERTIFICATIONS

◆ Docker Certified Associate, 2018